chinese-forums.com 2019-01-12

# Site privacy policy - Forums Usage and Help - Chinese-forums.com

Due to stuff you can read about [here](http://news.google.com/news/story?q=google+interest+based+ads&oe=utf-8&rls=org.mozilla:en-GB:official&client=firefox-a&um=1&ie=UTF-8&ncl=dC1WSFGagk9dsNMjK1ETEtoLumtYM&hl=en&ei=RhvBSci3FIG86gPGjbSwDQ&sa=X&oi=news_result&resnum=4&ct=more-results&cd=1), we need a privacy policy. As all I could come up with was 'Won't sell your email addresses, promise' I found one on the Internet. Sticking it up here for comments before making it official. 

For reference, the Adsense ads aren't shown to logged-in users currently. 

Privacy Policy for Chinese-forums.com 

The privacy of our visitors to Chinese-forums.com is important to us. 

At Chinese-forums.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Chinese-forums.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information, including email address, to third parties. 

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on Chinese-forums.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
